digitalchocolate.com 2013-05-13

# Privacy & Security | Digital Chocolate

### Your Privacy Matters to Us

Digital Chocolate, Inc. (“Digital Chocolate”, “We”, “we”, “us” or “our”) provides this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to inform our users (“users”, “your” or “you”) of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information we receive from users of http:// digitalchocolate.com (the “Site”), or any Digital Chocolate game provided on other websites or other  third party sources (collectively, the “Service”). This Policy does not apply to websites, applications or services that display or link to different privacy statements. Digital Chocolate is not responsible for the actions of third party people or companies, the content of their sites, the use of information you provide to them, or any products or services they may offer.  Any link to those sites does not constitute our sponsorship of, or affiliation with, those people or companies.

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. If we decide to change this Policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the date at the top of the page. The changes will be effective when posted, and your continued use of the Services after the effective date of such change constitutes your consent to the terms of the revised Policy. Please check this page on a regular basis and whenever you use the Services so that you remain aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

### Information Collection and Use ****

Digital Chocolate uses information, including personal information, that you provide or we collect to provide and enhance the Service, to improve our games and related services, and to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you. We may use the information we collect (a) to contact you about your use of the Service, such as for administrative purposes or to provide you with customer service; (b) to fulfill or respond to your requests, to process transactions, and to send you the communications you requested; (c) to notify you about important changes to our policies or Service, (d) to contact you regarding new and existing Digital Chocolate features, products and services, and special Digital Chocolate offers, promotions and events that we think you may find interesting and for other internal marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes; (e) to request feedback and to improve the Service and our product and service offerings, and develop new products and services; and (f) to provide product support.

When we use the term “personal information” in this Policy, it can include an individual’s first and last name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card or other account number. __

### _Via Social Networking Site_

**When you use a Digital Chocolate Service at a social networking site (“SNS”), you allow Digital Chocolate to access your profile information in accordance with the policies and terms of the SNS.**  
**Such information may include, but is not limited to, your first and last name, your profile picture, your SNS user ID and respective user IDs of your friends that are connected to the Service, your gender, your birthday, and your email address.**  
**In addition, Digital Chocolate may use some or all of your profile information as part of the features of the Service, such as game invites.   For example, your profile picture may be used in connection with an application so that others using the SNS may see your profile picture as they use that application.  Additionally, Digital Chocolate may use your profile picture in emails sent to individuals you chose to contact to invite to use the Service.  For example, Digital Chocolate may implement a feature so that each time you send a neighbor request or a game invite Digital Chocolate sends an email to that individual that includes your profile picture.**  
**The information you allow Digital Chocolate to access is affected by the privacy settings that you have set at the SNS. You may control and learn more about these privacy settings at the applicable SNS.**

**_Via User Registration_**  
When you register with Digital Chocolate, we may require you to provide information, such as your name, mobile telephone number, email address, a member name, and/or a PIN or password that will either be chosen by you or created for you by Digital Chocolate, credit card or other billing information and home and business postal address.  Additionally, we may also collect demographic information such as your date of birth, gender, hobbies, occupation, resume, company info, or computer or game related information. (collectively your “Account Information”). We use your Account Information to identify and communicate with you, such as in ratings, rankings, contests, special promotions and other activities in which you participate. Your member name may be viewable in communications with other members of the Service, so you should choose a member name that you are comfortable having displayed publicly.

**_Via Contests, Surveys and Other Activities_**  
Digital Chocolate may collect information, such as your name, address, telephone number, demographic information and information about your tastes and preferences when you enter a contest or sweepstakes or participate in a survey or similar activity on our Service. Additionally, you may be required to provide other information if you are selected as a winner in a contest or drawing.

**_Via Interactive Features_**  
We may collect your information in connection with interactive features of the Service, such as when you create a profile, send a wallpaper image to your phone, participate in discussions, leave comments or invite a friend. Additionally, information such as your performance or rank in games or applications, or your friends’ member names, may be associated with your member name and displayed on our Service.

When you participate in interactive areas of the Service, certain information you post is shared with other users. For example, information that you post in any comments, reviews, profiles, discussion groups or other interactive area, or other information that is provided for the purpose of being shared is publicly available to other users and can potentially be viewed by anyone.

**_Via Mobile Applications_**  
Some of our mobile applications may require you to input your wireless telephone number or other information into the application. We use this information in connection with providing the application, such as to authenticate you and to communicate with you regarding our services by SMS, text message or other electronic means to your mobile device.

In addition, when you use our mobile applications, your wireless device may transmit information about your activities in the application to our servers. We and service providers acting on our behalf may use tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information including device number, device identifiers, referring pages, the amount spend on particular mobile application, game state and the date and time of activity on our mobile application.  If an application includes any location-based services, your location may be shared with Digital Chocolate while using such feature.

**_Via Subscriptions, Resumes and Other Requests_**  
If you subscribe to the Digital Chocolate e-mail newsletter, request support, send us an email, submit a job application or resume or otherwise contact us through the Service, we collect information such as your name and email address and any other information you provide in such communication. We use such information that we collect in these manners to fulfill and contact you regarding your request and for the other purposes set forth in this policy.

**_Via Game Bars and Cross Promotion_**

The Service may display Digital Chocolate’s or a third party’s branded game bar (“Game Bar”) or other cross promotion tools that are used to cross promote Digital Chocolate’s Service and /or third party developer’s services. By clicking Digital Chocolate’s Service’s or a third party’s service’s icon, your user ID may be collected by the Game Bar and you will directed to the desired service.

We may also keep statistics of the Game Bar use on aggregate basis.

**_Via Log files_**  
When you access our Service, Digital Chocolate collects standard information about your computer/device, such as your IP address, browser type and operating system version. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Service, and to improve our products and services. This information may also be used to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you.  Digital Chocolate may determine your country and other physical location based on the information received from each connection.

### **_Via Cookies and Web Beacons_**

**The Site uses “cookies,” which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies are used to either identify you as a returning customer or improve the experience on our Service.**  
**Third parties that place advertising on our Service may also use cookies. Since the third party advertising companies tag your computer with a number, they will be able to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement.   These advertisers may use information about your visits to our Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.**  
Digital Chocolate uses “Clear GIFs” to analyze traffic on the Site, and within HTML e-mails to determine whether the e-mails have been opened. Clear GIFs (also called Web Beacons, or Web Bugs) are small images embedded on web pages and in email communications.

You may click on the following link: http://www.networkadvertising.org (or such other URL as may be specified by us from time to time) for information on how to opt-out of the use of cookies or Web beacons.

### Disclosure of Your Information

### **_Third Party Tools_**

The Service may also contain third party tracking tools from service providers, examples of which include Magic Box, Flurry and AdMob.  Digital Chocolate may use these third parties’ APIs/SDKs in our Service, which may enable these third parties to analyze user information.  While these third parties may have access to your personal information in connection with the performance of services for Digital Chocolate, they may not use such information for any purpose other than providing their services.

**_Service Providers and Affiliates_**

We may use third party companies to perform services related to  the Service and to assist in our marketing efforts.  These services may include, but are not limited to, maintenance services, data storage, database management, web analytics, payment processing, hosting services and email services.  They are obligated to use this information only to perform tasks on our behalf.

Digital Chocolate also may disclose or transfer your information to its corporate affiliates (for example, its subsidiaries or parent corporation).

**_Third Party Advertising_**

We may use, store and share with third party advertisers certain technical information (including IP addresses) or aggregated information of the users of Digital Chocolate’s Service such as general demographic and preference information. We may also allow advertisers to collect such technical or aggregate information that they may share with us. Such information collected may be used for industry analysis, demographic profiling and to deliver targeted advertising.

**_Offer Walls_**

The Service may display an “offer wall” that is hosted by an offer wall provider. The offer wall allows third party advertisers to provide virtual currency to users in exchange for completing an offer, fulfilling a survey or otherwise interacting with an advertisement. These are offers made by third party advertisers; not by Digital Chocolate.

These offers may be targeted to you based on certain information, such as your geographic area or other demographic information. After clicking on one of these advertisements, you will no longer be on a site hosted by Digital Chocolate orthe SNS.

We may need to share your user ID number with the offer wall provider. This identifier is used to ensure proper crediting of your account, prevent fraud or duplicate offers and to resolve any customer service inquiries that may arise. Once you complete an offer, you will then return to Digital Chocolate’s Service.

**_Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement_**

We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Digital Chocolate, such as to determine, bill and collect amounts owed to us, or to protect the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

**_Business Transfers_**

Digital Chocolate may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personal information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

**_Other Disclosures_**

•           Digital Chocolate may share your information when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies.

•           We may share aggregate or anonymous information about you with advertisers, publishers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

### How to Update Your Personal Information and Contact Preferences

If you wish to stop receiving marketing communications from us, you can opt out by replying to a message that we send you by clicking the unsubscribe link located on the bottom of the e-mail. If you opt-out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All users may review, update, correct or delete the information in their registration profile by changing the applicable information in their account settings or, for Services that are hosted on a SNS , by changing the applicable information in their profile page. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation to retain the record. See below for privacy contact information.

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Digital Chocolate. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### How We Protect Your Information

We have put reasonable security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, destruction and alteration of information under our control. For example, when you access your Account Information, we use the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol to encrypt information you input before it is sent to us.  
**Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we have procedures and security features in place to try to prevent unauthorized access.**

### A Note About Children

At Digital Chocolate, we understand that children’s privacy is important. Our Services are not intended for use by children aged 12 or younger, and we do not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from children aged 12 or younger. If you are 12 years old or younger, do not submit any personal information to Digital Chocolate. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 12 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 12, please contact us at webmaster@digitalchocolate.com.

### How to Contact Us

Digital Chocolate welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please give us your feedback via email to [support@digitalchocolate.com](mailto:support@digitalchocolate.com), or in writing to.

1855 South Grant Street, 2nd Fl

San Mateo, CA 94402

(Updated: 1/12/2012)
